{
    "subject": "resource/Dr\u00f8bak",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Norway",
    "human_readable": "Dr\u00f8bak is located in Norway.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9563524127006531,
            "question": "Where is Dr\u00f8bak located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9355548620223999,
            "question": "In what country is Dr\u00f8bak situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7577552795410156,
            "question": "Is Dr\u00f8bak a city or town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.722329318523407,
            "question": "What is the name of the country where Dr\u00f8bak resides?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6462221741676331,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.487429678440094,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions in Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4514678120613098,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4441109001636505,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43766510486602783,
            "question": "What is the population of Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3279402256011963,
            "question": "Does Dr\u00f8bak have a rich history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dr\u00f8bak is located in Norway.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5759_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Dr\u00f8bak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5759_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Dr\u00f8bak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5759_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Dr\u00f8bak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5759_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5759_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Dr\u00f8bak, including its location on the Oslo Fjord, south of Oslo (document 1), and its geographical coordinates (59.6633327, 10.6307414) which are also mentioned in document 6. These details suggest that Dr\u00f8bak is indeed located in Norway."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the location of Dr\u00f8bak, stating that it is situated on the Oslo Fjord and near Oslo, which confirms that Dr\u00f8bak is indeed located in Norway."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}